Annette Kar Baxter Papers, 1905-1984
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Writings
    - Research notes, "Freedom: Fun and Games," undated (Box 69)
    - Interview, "Follow a Star: Four Girls Interview their Heroines," Seventeen Magazine, Jan 1959 (Box 69)
  - Barnard College
    - Barnard Bulletin, 1954-78 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Barnard Bull, 2 Dec 1970 (Box 69)
    - Columbia Spectator, 1975-82 (Box 69)
    - University Committee on Rules of Conduct, undated (Box 69)
    - "A Model Bill of Rights and Responsibilities," Chronicle of Higher Education, 15 Mar 1971 (Box 69)
  - Other professional activities
    - American Association of University Women (Box 69)
      - AAUW New York Division Reports, 1975-77 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - AAUW New Yorker, 1977-82 (Box 69)
      - Poster, "An Evening with Margaret Mead," 1978 (Box 69)
    - Compton Advertising Awards: Poster, 1st Annual Advertising Journalism Awards, 1981 (Box 69)
    - Conference in Theology: "A Guide to Trinity College," undated (Box 69)
    - Encampment for Citizenship: "Freedom & Angelina," 1978 (Box 69)
    - Lotus Club: Poster, "State Dinner in Honor of President J. Roger Friedman, 1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files
    - American Studies (Box 69)
      - Conference: American Culture Association convention poster, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Programs, 1974-77, undated (Box 69)
    - Status of Women-International, 1970 (Box 69)
    - Women
      - Occupations (Box 69)
        - Medicine (Box 69)
        - "Langham's Pioneer Womanhood," 1963 (Box 69)
        - "Odessa Zionist Put Down in India," undated (Box 69)
    - Women's Studies
      - Publication notices, undated (Box 69)
      - Arno Press, undated (Box 69)
  - AAUW Insurance Plan poster, undated (Map-case Flat File)
  - Barnard's Women's Center brochure, "A Woman's Place in the World," undated (Map-case Flat File)
  - American Studies, publication notice: Temple University Press, circa 1980 (Map-case Flat File)
  - Women's Studies, publication notices, 1972-82, undated (Map-case Flat File)